# AbdulSamad Ayoade

hi@abdulsamad.xyz



08160500329



linkedin.com/in/abdulsamad-ayoade



https://abdulsamad.xyz

# Summary

I am a self-taught frontend developer specializing in core frontend technologies HTML, CSS, SCSS, TailwindCSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, Vue JS, ReactJS and NextJS but is passionate about all aspects of technologies. I am experienced at implementing pixel perfect and functional web applications.

# **Experience**



# Frontend Developer

WUNDER WERKZ

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022 (4 months)

#### **Product Engineer**

Business Process Technologies Nigeria Apr 2022 - Jun 2022 (3 months)

#### Front End Engineer

Business Process Technologies Nigeria Oct 2021 - Mar 2022 (6 months)

#### **Education**



# Usmanu Danfodiyo University, Sokoto

Bachelor's, Economics 2015 - 2019

#### **Skills**

NextJS • SCSS • React Hooks • React.js • Next.js • Redux.js • Tailwind CSS • Cascading Style Sheets (CSS) • WordPress • PHP